I wear a watch kind of weird. I wear it
to where the face is on the bottom here.
So, I raise it up and look at it like
that. I saw an older gentleman doing
that when I was a kid. So, I've always
done that. Anyway, long story short, it
scratches up your watch face. So, this
one scratched all, you know, this is
just scratched like crazy. This is an
Apple Watch. It scratched all up and I
just kind of thought if I ever get
another Apple Watch, I'm going to
protect it and get a screen protector
for it. So today we're going to be
testing out the Magic John screen
protectors for Apple watches. Anyway,
these are around $15 on Amazon. I will
have an Amazon link in the description
of this video and also one in the
comments if you want to check one of
these out after the video. Let's get
started.
So this is what this contraption comes
in. It just comes in a block a box like
this. And I'm just going to open this up
and we're going to take a quick look at
it and then get this thing going. So
that's what this whole device looks
like. We're going to open it up and
there's little prep stuff in here. and a
set of instructions and you can also
follow a QR code. And this thing has got
two setups in here. So, you've got two
screen protectors in here and actually
two, you know, whole kits really uh
because you can, you know, do this twice
if need be. And right there, you saw me
my watch without a band in there, but if
you got a regular size band, it'll fit
in there. I just have that wide one, so
I just had to take my watch out itself
and stick it in there. Okay, the first
step is just cleaning it off this little
alcohol pad or what I don't really know
what the chemical is, but I'm wiping it
down and you just get it real good and
clean. And it's supposed to be three
steps. And the next part of this is a um
it's like a little cleansing cloth. It's
sort of like a just a very tiny mini
dust cloth. And I'd use that to sort of
dry this thing and just clean it a
little better. you know, if you read the
instructions, it probably tells you a
little different, but uh you know,
you're supposed to be, you know, using
the cleaner, the wipe, and then the
little dust sticker that comes with it.
So, that's the three steps. And I did
not use the dust sticker cuz I didn't
think I needed it. So, anyway, after you
get it all good and clean, then you're
going to get this thing set up to go.
And you see this is the way it's
supposed to be set up. That little
orange bar is all the way to the top
like that. And then we're going to get
our little screen protector out. that's
in that little piece of uh wax paper or
whatever the heck that is. Little
plastic bag. And then we're going to
stick it in here. Now, you see that it's
got four corners to it. And you you
shove them on the little orange pegs.
So, just like I'm doing right there.
That's how this thing goes in. Once you
get it locked into those pegs,
there's a little flap
on the front underneath there. That's
that's actually with the screen
protector. And uh you make sure that
flaps out so that you can pull it out
once you get the lid closed on this
thing.
Okay. Now you can pull that little flap
out. That's the dust remover or dust
protector or whatever they call it. And
once that's out, then you start this
process. You just push this all the way
down. And then you'll pull it all the
way back.
And once you get that all the way back,
this thing is done. The screen protector
is on there. So just pop it back open.
Get all this stuff out of the way and
you've got your little watch in there
with the screen protector on it. It's
that simple. And you can see here it
goes right to the edge of the top. It
doesn't go it doesn't cover the entire
surface. Obviously, the little rounded
part at the bottom on the sides there is
not covered. So, I think they do this
because if they cover the entire top of
the watch, then it would probably uh you
know, start to pull up. So, it's a
little bit, you know, made to where it's
just sort of flat on that flat surface
on the front of this watch. Anyway,
that's pretty easy to do. And if you
need instructions, QR code, whatever,
you can follow that. And uh that's what
it looks like when it's done. And I'm
going to show you right now. This is a
week later. So, this is what this thing
looks like after I've wore this watch
upside down and beat it up against
counters and everything else inside cars
and you name it. I think I even worked
on a car maybe a little bit with this
thing on. I'm not really sure if I did
or not, but anyway, uh I give this thing
a beating, you know, wearing it upside
down. And you can see it looks pretty
good for that. So, I give this thing an
A+ so far. I don't know how long it's
going to last, but so far so good. I
really like it. Again, there will be an
Amazon link in the description of this
video and also in the comments if you
want to check one of these out after the
video. And anyway, they're about $15 and
you get two to do this. So, you know, if
you screw it up, you can do it again.
or, you know, maybe if the thing wears
out or starts looking bad, you can, you
know, get it out of the drawer and put a
new one on. Please remember to subscribe
to my channel. If you have any questions
about these screen protectors, please
throw it down in my comments. Or if you
just want to say a friendly word, throw
it down in the comments. I want to thank
you so much for tuning in to Tony's
Reviews today and God bless